articleswale.com 2013-04-15

# Privacy Policy

###  1 Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy. ](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

### 2\. Acceptance of Terms of service

By accessing the website, visiting the website or linking to the website, you acknowledge that you have read the following Terms of use.

### 3\. Service we provide

We provide service to registered as well as non-registered users. While registered users can view as well as submit the articles, non-registered users can only view the articles.

### 4\. Information needed for registration

we collect Personal information from you when you register on our site. When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address and password.

### 5\. Licence for Author work

Author work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. You can use or distribute author work in compliance of the conditions specified in section 5. 

### 6\. Use of Author work

You can use Author work provided

  1. a. You can not alter or modify the content.
  2. b. You will keep Author name intact.
  3. c. You will include link back to the original content.

### 7\. Intellectual Property

The site, all the services and other content including design, graphics, text, copyright, technical data, logo , source code (collectively Intellectual Property) excluding author work are property of site owners.

### 8\. Restrictions

You are not allowed to

  1. a. put abusive, vulgar content on the site.
  2. b. put content on the site under your name which is owned by someone else.

### 9\. Privacy Policy

Please also read our Privacy Policy on <http://www.articleswale.com/>.

### 10\. Change of Terms of service

We reserve the right to change Terms of service at any time. So, Please read Terms of use before use of this site.

### 11\. Contact us

If you have any queries, you can contact us on <http://www.articleswale.com/>.
